Kiran Veerabhadranavar

Software Engineer

Contact PHONE +919663358955 EMAIL kiranveerabhadranavar847@gmail.com ADDRESS Belgaum, Karnataka in LinkedIn www.linkedin.com/in/kiran-veer Website www.kiranveer.tech

SKILLS

Technical Skills

Java | C++ | C# | Git | HTML | Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) | Oracle SQL | Algorithms and data structures | C | Javascript | React Js | Bootstrap | Redux | Material-UI | ES6 | MongoDB | Node Js | Express Js | Rest API | Github

Soft Skills

Critical thinking | Multitasking abilities | Teamwork

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Achieved Excellence in Company training and training test.
- Secured 13th Rank in NMMS National level Examination 2013.
- Won Best Final year project award.
- Won 2nd Prize for Social Innovation Project.
- Won 3rd Prize for 2nd year project.

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

- · Stock Market Trading
- Travelling
- Learning New Things

SUMMARY

Software Engineer with over 1 Year of successful experience in Software Development and Software Testing. Recognized consistently for performance excellence and contributions to success in IT industry. Strengths in **Java** and **DSA** backed by training in **MERN Stack Development**.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Aug 2022 - Present	Software Engineer Persistent Systems Ltd., Pune, Maharashtra
	 Successfully completed 3 months of training in different technologies. Managed to gain more than 8 skills during the training period. Contributed ideas and suggestions in team meetings and delivered updates on deadlines, designs and enhancements.
Oct 2020 - Dec 2020	Web Developer (Internship) Flying Brains Innovations Pvt Ltd., Dharwar, Karnataka

- Produced more than 5 sample sites within 3 months and received feedback about draft sites.
- **Boosted user functionality** by developing seamless website design, usability and technology.

CGPA: 8.03

EDUCATION

Aug 2018 -

Jul 2022	Communication KLE Dr M S Sheshgiri College of Engineering and Technology	J
Jun 2016 - May 2018	PUC: Science R L PU College of Science, Belagavi	85.67%
Jun 2013 - May 2016	Secondary Education B K Model High School, Belagavi	91.20%

B.E: Electronics and

PROJECTS

Mar 2023 - Mar 2023	Portfolio - https://www.kiranveer.tech • Created my own Portfolio site using React js in 10 days.
Feb 2023 - Feb 2023	MeTube - https://metube.kiranveer.tech • Created Youtube clone using RapidAPI, React and Material-UI in 20 days.
Apr 2023 - Apr 2023	techPunch - https://www.techpunch.in Created website for a Startup called techPunch using React and Material-UI within 15 days.